let MCQS = [
  {
    question: "Who among the following has invented worldwide web?",
    choice1: "Tim Berners-Lee",
    choice2: "George Boole",
    choice3: "Jean Bartik",
    choice4: "Per Brinch Hansen",
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which company created the most used networking software in the 1980's?",
    choice1: "Microsoft",
    choice2: "Novell",
    choice3: "IBM",
    choice4: "Sun",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: " What skills do you need to be a business manager?",
    choice1: "All of the below",
    choice2: "Leadership",
    choice3: "Critical Thinking",
    choice4: "Communication",
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most popular career in psychology?",
    choice1: "Sport psychology",
    choice2: "Clinical psychology",
    choice3: "Forensic psychology",
    choice4: "Counseling psychology",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the youngest lawyer in the wolrd?",
    choice1: "Stephan Baccus aka",
    choice2: "Danya Hamad",
    choice3: "Seth Harding",
    choice4: "Kelly Yang",
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "In wihich decade was the Internet First Implemented?",
    choice1: "1950s",
    choice2: "1960s",
    choice3: "1940s",
    choice4: "1980s",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the highest paid business man?",
    choice1: "Warren Buffet",
    choice2: "Jeff Bezos",
    choice3: "Elon Musk",
    choice4: "Larry Ellison",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the famous man in psychology?",
    choice1: "Jean Piaget",
    choice2: "Sigmund Freud",
    choice3: "Albert Bandura",
    choice4: "Carl Rogers",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who amoung the following is the founder of the world economic forum?",
    choice1: "Robert Zoellick",
    choice2: "Klaus Schwab",
    choice3: "John Kenneth Galaraith",
    choice4: "Paul Krugman",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the legan advisor to the government of a state in India?",
    choice1: "The Solicitor",
    choice2: "The Advocate General",
    choice3: "The High Court",
    choice4: "The State Chief Legal Officer",
    answer: 1,
  },
];
